Register of the Raymond Moley papers, 1902-1971
Hoover Institution Archives
- GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE, 1912-1969 (Boxes 2-62)
  - Schramm, Gustav L., 1929-1934 (Folder 63)
  - Schricker, Henry F., 1948 (Folder 64)
  - Schroder, Andrew J., 1929 (Folder 65)
  - Schroth, Thomas N., 1961 (Folder 66)
  - Schufe, W. A., 1919 (Folder 67)
  - Schurman, n.d. (Folder 68)
  - Schuster, M. L., 1939 (Folder 69)
  - Schwartz, Arthur, 1929-1934 (Folder 70)
  - Schwartzman, J. Anthony, 1932 (Folder 71)
  - Schwemler, Frank J., 1951 (Folder 72)
  - Schweppe, Alfred J., 1953 (Folder 73)
  - Schwerin, Charles, 1932 (Folder 74)
  - Schwin, Newell T., 1951 (Folder 75)
  - Scoggins, Verne, 1950-1951 (Folder 76)
  - Scott, Duncan, 1961 (Folder 77)
  - Scott, Herbert, 1934 (Folder 78)
  - Scott, Hugh, 1962-1964 (Folder 79)
  - Scott, Hugh D., 1927 (Folder 80)
  - Scott, Philip Gordon, 1927 (Folder 81)
  - Scott, W. Kerr, 1951-1952 (Folder 82)
  - Scoville, John W., 1942 (Folder 83)
  - Scragg, George H., 1943 (Folder 84)
  - Scragg, Harold A., 1927-1928 (Folder 85)
  - Seabury, Samuel, 1931-1932 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Seager, Henry R., 1930 (Folder 2)
  - Seamans, William S., 1932 (Folder 3)
  - Searls, Virginia, 1946 (Folder 4)
  - Seaver, Charles H., 1922 (Folder 5)
  - Securities Service Corporation, 1933 (Folder 6)
  - Seelye, G. Carr, 1932 (Folder 7)
  - Seibels, William T., 1933 (Folder 8)
  - Selby, John, 1939 (Folder 9)
  - Seldes, Gilbert, 1938 (Folder 10)
  - Selekman, Ben M., 1933 (Folder 11)
  - Seligman, Eustace, 1936 (Folder 12)
  - Sell, Henry Blackman, 1937 (Folder 13)
  - Seller, Barbara F., 1951 (Folder 14)
  - Sellers, James T., 1957-1958 (Folder 15)
  - Sellin, Thorsten, 1928-1929 (Folder 16)
  - Seltzer, Julian, 1929 (Folder 17)
  - Seltzer, Louis, 1923-1958 (Folder 18)
  - Selvage, James P., 1943 (Folder 19)
  - Sennings, John P., 1931 (Folder 20)
  - Seo, S., 1959 (Folder 21)
  - Serena, Anne, 1951 (Folder 22)
  - Servies, James A., 1964 (Folder 23)
  - Sessions, Juliette, 1918 (Folder 24)
  - Settle, T. S., 1931-1932 (Folder 25)
  - Sevey, Mrs. George, 1932 (Folder 26)
  - Sewell, Henry, 1914 (Folder 27)
  - Sexton, Brendan, 1957 (Folder 28)
  - Sexton, Robert H., 1932 (Folder 29)
  - Seymour, Gideon D., 1947-1950 (Folder 30)
  - Shakespeare, M., 1942 (Folder 31)
  - Shalloo, J. P., 1931 (Folder 32)
  - Shambaugh, Ben F., 1930 (Folder 33)
  - Sharon, J. A., 1921 (Folder 34)
  - Sharp, Walter R., 1930 (Folder 35)
  - Sharp, Roland Hall, 1934 (Folder 36)
  - Shartel, Burke, 1931 (Folder 37)
  - Shaughnessey, Edward J., 1937 (Folder 38)
  - Shaw, 1940 (Folder 39)
  - Shaw, A. Vere, 1933 (Folder 40)
  - Shaw, Arch W., 1948 (Folder 41)
  - Shaw, Chet, 1940 (Folder 42)
  - Shaw, William, 1965 (Folder 43)
  - Sheaffer, Craig R., 1944-1945 (Folder 44)
  - Sheaffer, W. A., 1932-1940 (Folder 45)
  - Shearn, Clarence J., 1933 (Folder 46)
  - Sheffield, James R., 1936 (Folder 47)
  - Shepard, William, 1932 (Folder 48)
  - Sherley, Swagar, 1937 (Folder 49)
  - Sherr, Arthur, 1905 (Folder 50)
  - Sherrill, George R., 1928-1929 (Folder 51)
  - Sherwin, Belle, 1924-1929 (Folder 52)
  - Shields, Leighton, 1932 (Folder 53)
  - Shields, Permelia, 1931 (Folder 54)
  - Shientag, Bernard, 1936 (Folder 55)
  - Shirrell, Elmer L., 1927 (Folder 56)
  - Shively, George, 1926 (Folder 57)
  - Shivers, Allan, 1952 (Folder 58)
  - Shockley, W. T., 1934 (Folder 59)
  - Shoop, John W., 1936 (Folder 60)
  - Short, William H., 1923 (Folder 61)
  - Shotwell, James T., 1932 (Folder 62)
  - Shouse, Jouett, 1933-1939 (Folder 63)
  - Shrifts, Bernice, 1933 (Folder 64)
  - Schulman, 1927 (Folder 65)
  - Shuman, Charles, 1961 (Folder 66)
  - Shuman, W. Irving, 1932 (Folder 67)
  - Shurrill, George, 1927 (Folder 68)
  - Shuster, George N., 1934 (Folder 69)
  - Shule, Marian, 1936 (Folder 70)
  - Sibley, H. E., 1942 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Sieverman, Frank, 1936 (Folder 2)
  - Sifton, Harry, 1933 (Folder 3)
  - Sihler, Christian, 1919 (Folder 4)
  - Silbert, Samuel, 1964 (Folder 5)
  - Sill, Frederick H., 1936 (Folder 6)
  - Silverman, Harriet, 1920 (Folder 7)
  - Simerah, Isabel, 1919 (Folder 8)
  - Simkhovich, Vladimir, 1936 (Folder 9)
  - Simmons, H. E., 1919 (Folder 10)
  - Simms, Albert G., 1950 (Folder 11)
  - Simms, Ruth H., 1944 (Folder 12)
  - Simon, Caroline K., 1941-1960 (Folder 13)
  - Simon, M., 1942 (Folder 14)
  - Simpson, Ethel, 1964-1965 (Folder 15)
  - Simpson, David P., 1923-1925 (Folder 16)
  - Simpson, Smith, 1933 (Folder 17)
  - Sinclair, Stanley, 1959 (Folder 18)
  - Sinclair, Upton, 1933-1958 (Folder 19)
  - Siousset, Helen J., 1939 (Folder 20)
  - Sisson, Daniel, 1966 (Folder 21)
  - Sisson, Edgar, 1934 (Folder 22)
  - Sisson, Edward, 1943 (Folder 23)
  - Sizoo, Joseph A., 1963 (Folder 24)
  - Skeel, Lee, 1922 (Folder 25)
  - Skeels, Homer L., 1929 (Folder 26)
  - Skinner, R. Dana, 1935 (Folder 27)
  - Slane, Henry D., 1961 (Folder 28)
  - Slaughter, Roger C., 1948 (Folder 29)
  - Slawson, John, 1928 (Folder 30)
  - Slechta, Joseph J., 1938 (Folder 31)
  - Sleeper, Clarence, 1951 (Folder 32)
  - Sleszynski, Thaddeus, 1920 (Folder 33)
  - Slichter, Sumner H., 1940 (Folder 34)
  - Sloan, Alfred P., 1937 (Folder 35)
  - Slocum, Kay, 1962 (Folder 36)
  - Smathers, George A., 1953 (Folder 37)
  - Smeeth, Harwood E., 1942 (Folder 38)
  - Smethurst, R. S., 1958 (Folder 39)
  - Smith, A. Calvert, 1943-1945 (Folder 40)
  - Smith, Alfred E., 1929-1944 (Folder 41)
  - Smith, Bruce "C.B.", 1927-1934 (Folder 42)
  - Smith, C. R., 1941 (Folder 43)
  - Smith, Carl D., 1937 (Folder 44)
  - Smith, Courtland, 1933 (Folder 45)
  - Smith, Dwight E., 1923 (Folder 46)
  - Smith, Elliot D., 1939-1942 (Folder 47)
  - Smith, Evelyn E., 1929-1930 (Folder 48)
  - Smith, G. B. E., 1923 (Folder 49)
  - Smith, Geddes, 1923 (Folder 50)
  - Smith, Helen May, 1931 (Folder 51)
  - Smith, Herbert L., 1928 (Folder 52)
  - Smith, Herman, 1938 (Folder 53)
  - Smith, Howard J., 1961 (Folder 54)
  - Smith, Howard L., 1936 (Folder 55)
  - Smith, Howard W., 1929-1941 (Folder 56)
  - Smith, James, 1938 (Folder 57)
  - Smith, Lawrence H., 1952 (Folder 58)
  - Smith, Lysander, 1931 (Folder 59)
  - Smith, Mariana, 1929 (Folder 60)
  - Smith, P. M., 1934 (Folder 61)
  - Smith, Paul, 1950 (Folder 62)
  - Smith, Paul C., 1939-1952 (Folder 63)
  - Smith, Ralph H., 1961 (Folder 64)
  - Smith, Reginald, 1949 (Folder 65)
  - Smith, Rex, 1938-1939 (Folder 66)
  - Smith, Richard R., 1930 (Folder 67)
  - Smith, Richard W., 1963 (Folder 68)
  - Smith, Rixey, 1939 (Folder 69)
  - Smith, Sylvester, 1937 (Folder 70)
  - Smith, Tom K., 1936-1951 (Folder 71)
  - Smith, W. C., 1932 (Folder 72)
  - Smith, W. W., 1933 (Folder 73)
  - Smith, William A., 1945 (Folder 74)
  - Smith, Young B., 1928-1933 (Folder 75)
  - Smoker, E. H., 1963 (Folder 76)
  - Smoleff, Samuel, 1929 (Folder 77)
  - Smoot, Reed, 1937 (Folder 78)
  - Smylie, Robert, 1951-1963 (Folder 79)
  - Snaddon, Andy, 1957-1958 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Snevilly, Henry M., 1944 (Folder 2)
  - Snodgrass, May Hess, 1944-1961 (Folder 3)
  - Snow, Henry N., 1924 (Folder 4)
  - Snow, W. G., 1936 (Folder 5)
  - Snyder, Carl, 1928 (Folder 6)
  - Snyder, Mrs. Charles, 1937 (Folder 7)
  - Snyder, Hubert, 1953 (Folder 8)
  - Snyder, Richard, 1951 (Folder 9)
  - Sokolsky, George, 1948 (Folder 10)
  - Solberg, Thorvald, 1918 (Folder 11)
  - Solicitor General, 1936 (Folder 12)
  - Solomon, Walter Leo, 1918 (Folder 13)
  - Solomont, James, 1934 (Folder 14)
  - Sommers, Martin, 1946 (Folder 15)
  - Sonsteby, John J., 1932 (Folder 16)
  - Soskin, William, 1932 (Folder 17)
  - Sousa, Barbara, 1964 (Folder 18)
  - Southard, L. G., 1932 (Folder 19)
  - Southwick, Grace R., 1937 (Folder 20)
  - Spackman, Peter, 1963-1965 (Folder 21)
  - Spahr, Walter E., 1932 (Folder 22)
  - Spangler, Harrison E., 1943 (Folder 23)
  - Sparrow, W. K., 1934 (Folder 24)
  - Spellman, Francis Cardinal, 1945-1964 (Folder 25)
  - Spencer, H. L., 1923-1946 (Folder 26)
  - Spencer, Henry R., 1920 (Folder 27)
  - Sperling, Isidor, 1930 (Folder 28)
  - Spiller, Caryl, 1919 (Folder 29)
  - Spitzer, Adelbert, 1912 (Folder 30)
  - Spivak, L. E., 1934-1938 (Folder 31)
  - Sporn, Philip, 1956 (Folder 32)
  - Sprague, Albert A., 1931 (Folder 33)
  - Sprague, J. Russel, 1948 (Folder 34)
  - Sprague, L. C., 1943-1944 (Folder 35)
  - Staatz, L. N., 1937 (Folder 36)
  - Stace, Arthur W., 1941 (Folder 37)
  - Stackland, Karl V., 1932 (Folder 38)
  - Stackpole Company, 1953 (Folder 39)
  - Staehling, Ethel G., 1937 (Folder 40)
  - Stafford, B. L., 1932 (Folder 41)
  - Stafford, Burt, 1943 (Folder 42)
  - Stahl, Steve, 1961 (Folder 43)
  - Stahlman, James G., 1951-1962 (Folder 44)
  - Stanley, C. M., 1937 (Folder 45)
  - Stanley, W. F., 1932-1934 (Folder 46)
  - Stans, Maurice, 1959 (Folder 47)
  - Stark, Lloyd E., 1942 (Folder 48)
  - Stark, Paul, 1941 (Folder 49)
  - Starr, Louis M., 1965 (Folder 50)
  - Starr, W. A., 1932-1939 (Folder 51)
  - Stassen, Harold E., 1947-1948 (Folder 52)
  - Stegall, Henry, 1934 (Folder 53)
  - Steanstein, B., 1931 (Folder 54)
  - Stearns, Harold C., 1953 (Folder 55)
  - Stearns, Orsa, 1934 (Folder 56)
  - Stedman, A. D., 1934 (Folder 57)
  - Steelman, Mrs. A. J., 1925 (Folder 58)
  - Steever, Miller, 1930 (Folder 59)
  - Steinbrook, S., 1945 (Folder 60)
  - Steiner, Jesse, 1926-1930 (Folder 61)
  - Steinhart, L., n.d. (Folder 62)
  - Steinmetz, G. M., 1937-1942 (Folder 63)
  - Stephens, J. Paul, 1963 (Folder 64)
  - Stephenson, Francis, 1948 (Folder 65)
  - Stephenson, Harold, 1929 (Folder 66)
  - Stern, Leon, 1930 (Folder 67)
  - Sterling, D. J., 1943-1953 (Folder 68)
  - Sternberg, Louis, 1932 (Folder 69)
  - Stettinius, E. R., Jr., 1944 (Folder 70)
  - Stevehardt, L., 1933 (Folder 71)
  - Steven, W. P., 1961 (Folder 72)
  - Stevens, Helen K., 1929 (Folder 73)
  - Stevens, R. B., 1929 (Folder 74)
  - Stevens, Samuel N., 1941 (Folder 75)
  - Stevenson, Adlai, 1952-1953 (Folder 76)
  - Stevenson, John A., 1947 (Folder 77)
  - Stevenson, Mrs. John A., 1949 (Folder 78)
  - Stevenson, Robert E., n.d. (Folder 79)
  - Stewart, D. E., 1921 (Folder 80)
  - Stewart, Irwin, 1929 (Folder 81)
  - Stewart, Jack, 1931-1963 (Folder 82)
  - Stewart, Raymond, n.d. (Folder 83)
  - Stewart, Robert, 1941 (Folder 84)
  - Stewart, Tom, 1946 (Folder 85)
  - Stewart, William, 1939 (Folder 86)
  - Stiles, Charles E., 1951 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Stilwell, Charles, 1943 (Folder 2)
  - Stimson, George P., 1953 (Folder 3)
  - Stinchcomb, W. A., 1933 (Folder 4)
  - Stires, Evelyn, 1932 (Folder 5)
  - Stittson, E. P., 1944 (Folder 6)
  - Stock, David, 1934 (Folder 7)
  - Stockdale, T. R., 1953-1954 (Folder 8)
  - Stocks, C. Wallace, 1934 (Folder 9)
  - Stockton, W. L., 1937 (Folder 10)
  - Stolberg, Benjamin, 1939 (Folder 11)
  - Stokes, Rose Pastor, 1927 (Folder 12)
  - Stone, Alice, 1930 (Folder 13)
  - Stone, Donald C., 1928-1930 (Folder 14)
  - Stone, Harlan F., 1929 (Folder 15)
  - Stone, O. R., 1912 (Folder 16)
  - Storey, Douglass, 1950 (Folder 17)
  - Storke, Charles, 1937-1942 (Folder 18)
  - Storke, Susan, 1927 (Folder 19)
  - Storke, Thomas M., 1937-1961 (Folder 20)
  - Storms, Albert B., 1924-1931 (Folder 21)
  - Story, Russell, 1938 (Folder 22)
  - Stowe, A. M., 1919 (Folder 23)
  - Strain, Thomas B., 1949 (Folder 24)
  - Strand, William C., 1956 (Folder 25)
  - Stranger, Francis A., 1931 (Folder 26)
  - Strasburger, L., 1952 (Folder 27)
  - Stratton, Owen S., 1955 (Folder 28)
  - Straus, Dorothy, 1925 (Folder 29)
  - Straus, Jesse I., n.d. (Folder 30)
  - Straus, Michael, 1932 (Folder 31)
  - Straus, Nathan, 1934 (Folder 32)
  - Straus, Percy, 1938 (Folder 33)
  - Straus, Roger, Jr., 1952 (Folder 34)
  - Straus, Roger K., 1939 (Folder 35-36)
  - Strauss, Julius, 1934 (Folder 37)
  - Strauss, Lewis, 1957-1959 (Folder 38)
  - Strauss, W. A., 1963 (Folder 39)
  - Street, Elwood, 1919 (Folder 40)
  - Street, Julian, 1937 (Folder 41)
  - Stringfellow, George E., 1943-1944 (Folder 42)
  - Strode, Hudson, 1964-1965 (Folder 43)
  - Strong, Daniel U., 1936 (Folder 44)
  - Strother, Robert S., 1965 (Folder 45)
  - Strouse, Norman H., 1955 (Folder 46)
  - Strout, Richard (Folder 47)
  - Struelens, Michel, 1962 (Folder 48)
  - Stuart, Carl, 1942 (Folder 49)
  - Studebaker, J. W., 1932 (Folder 50)
  - Sturges, Kenneth, 1924 (Folder 51)
  - Sturges, Wesley M., 1927 (Folder 52)
  - Styles and Cash, Inc., 1933 (Folder 53)
  - Styles, William, 1931 (Folder 54)
  - Stylus, Ralph, n.d. (Folder 55)
  - Suhrie, Ambrose C., 1918-1955 (Folder 56)
  - Sulka, A., 1942 (Folder 57)
  - Sullivan, Mark, 1934-1936 (Folder 58)
  - Sulzberger, Arthur H., 1930-1938 (Folder 59)
  - Summerfield, Arthur E., 1955 (Folder 60)
  - Sumner, G. Lynn, 1937 (Folder 61)
  - Sumners, Hatton W., 1934-1942 (Folder 62)
  - Superintendent of Schools, Ohio, 1918 (Folder 63)
  - Supreme Court of the United States, 1930 (Folder 64)
  - Suralt, Valeska, 1934 (Folder 65)
  - Survey Association, 1929 (Folder 66)
  - Survey Committee, Chicago Police Department, 1932 (Folder 67)
  - Sutherland, E. H., 1928-1929 (Folder 68)
  - Sutton, K. A., 1933 (Folder 69)
  - Sutton, Louis, 1957 (Folder 70)
  - Swager, Sherley, 1936 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Swain, R. L., 1932 (Folder 2)
  - Swan, D. Walter, 1958 (Folder 3)
  - Swan, Natalie, 1924 (Folder 4)
  - Swarthout, John, 1951 (Folder 5)
  - Sweeney, Martin C., 1932-1934 (Folder 6)
  - Sweet, William, 1936 (Folder 7)
  - Swifter, 1946 (Folder 8)
  - Swigert, Ernest, 1949-1960 (Folder 9)
  - Swiggert, E. B., 1927 (Folder 10)
  - Swing, Raymond, 1936 (Folder 11)
  - Swope, Gerard, 1934-1936 (Folder 12)
  - Swope, Herbert Bayard, 1932-1955 (Folder 13)
  - Swope, Mrs. Herbert Bayard, 1958 (Folder 14)
  - Symonds, R. H., 1936 (Folder 15)
  - Synhorst, M., 1961 (Folder 16)
  - Taber, John, 1954-1955 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Tabor, L. L., 1934 (Folder 2)
  - Tachau, Charles G., 1932 (Folder 3)
  - Taft, Charles P., 1933-1936 (Folder 4)
  - Taft, Donald F., 1919 (Folder 5)
  - Taft, Hulbert, 1950 (Folder 6)
  - Taft, Robert A., 1939-1942 (Folder 7)
  - Taft, William H., 1927-1929 (Folder 8)
  - Taggert, S. W., 1932 (Folder 9)
  - Tamkin, Jeffrey H., 1963 (Folder 10)
  - Tamm, Quinn, 1965 (Folder 11)
  - Tance, Margaret, 1961 (Folder 12)
  - Tankersley, G. J., 1963 (Folder 13)
  - Tannenbaum, Frank, 1932 (Folder 14)
  - Tanning, Phineas H., 1934 (Folder 15)
  - Tansil, John, 1937 (Folder 16)
  - Tavel, William Saxby, 1963 (Folder 17)
  - Taylor, C. J., 1953 (Folder 18)
  - Taylor, Frank J., 1943 (Folder 19)
  - Taylor, Henry J., 1942-1962 (Folder 20)
  - Taylor, Horace, 1928-1933 (Folder 21)
  - Taylor, John H., Jr., 1929 (Folder 22)
  - Taylor, Leroy T., 1960 (Folder 23)
  - Taylor, Lynn, 1956 (Folder 24)
  - Taylor, Reese H., 1950-1960 (Folder 25)
  - Taylor, Wayne C., 1932 (Folder 26)
  - Taylor, William T., 1927 (Folder 27)
  - Tead, Ordway, 1929-1934 (Folder 28)
  - Teague, Charles M., 1960 (Folder 29)
  - Telford, Fred, 1932 (Folder 30)
  - Tennant, Anna Marie, 1934 (Folder 31)
  - Terry, William E., 1952 (Folder 32)
  - Thayer, V. T., 1923 (Folder 33)
  - Thayer, Walter N., 1962 (Folder 34)
  - Thomajan, P. K., 1934 (Folder 35)
  - Thomas, Charles Swain, 1939 (Folder 36)
  - Thomas, E. R., 1932 (Folder 37)
  - Thomas, Franklin, 1951 (Folder 38)
  - Thomas, Lowell, 1940 (Folder 39)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1929 (Folder 40)
  - Thomas, Paul B., 1930-1934 (Folder 41)
  - Thomas, Theodore, 1945 (Folder 42)
  - Thomas, William I., 1923 (Folder 43)
  - Thompson, Amos Burt, 1923-1960 (Folder 44)
  - Thompson, Carl, 1934 (Folder 45)
  - Thompson, Dorothy, 1937 (Folder 46)
  - Thompson, Edward, 1958 (Folder 47)
  - Thompson, Frank V., 1919 (Folder 48)
  - Thompson, George Jarvis, 1930 (Folder 49)
  - Thompson, Guy A., 1937-1942 (Folder 50)
  - Thompson, Lockwood, 1934 (Folder 51)
  - Thompson, T. Harry, 1937 (Folder 52)
  - Thompson, W. S., 1924 (Folder 53)
  - Thomson, George F., 1930 (Folder 54)
  - Thomson, J. M., 1934 (Folder 55)
  - Thomson, W. D., 1944-1945 (Folder 56)
  - Thorne, Florence B., 1965 (Folder 57)
  - Thornton, John L., 1933 (Folder 58)
  - Thorp, Helen Stanley, 1929 (Folder 59)
  - Thorpe, Merle, 1942 (Folder 60)
  - Thrasher, Frederic M., 1931 (Folder 61)
  - Thurmond, Strom, 1961 (Folder 62)
  - Thurston, Elliott, 1936-1954 (Folder 63)
  - Thurston, Henry W., 1931 (Folder 64)
  - Thwing, Charles F., 1919-1924 (Folder 65)
  - Tibbett, Lawrence, 1948 (Folder 66)
  - Tiesort, Francis J., 1930 (Folder 67)
  - Tiffany, Charles L., 1924 (Folder 68)
  - Tilton, Edwin O., 1939 (Folder 69)
  - Tilton, George F., 1938 (Folder 70)
  - Tilton, L. Deming, 1936 (Folder 71)
  - Timken, Henry H., 1963 (Folder 72)
  - Timmons, Bascom N., 1948-1955 (Folder 73)
  - Tinkham, George Holden, 1953 (Folder 74)
  - Titterton, L. H., 1930 (Folder 75)
  - Tittmann, Hilgard F., 1933 (Folder 76)
  - Titus, Charles H., 1932 (Folder 77)
  - Tobias, Paul H., 1958 (Folder 78)
  - Tobin, Maurice J., 1951 (Folder 79)
  - Tobin, Richard L., 1961 (Folder 80)
  - Todd, Arthur J., 1919-1921 (Folder 81)
  - Toles, Elsie, 1921 (Folder 82)
  - Tolley, William Pearson, 1937 (Folder 83)
  - Tolman, Edgar B., 1931 (Folder 84)
  - Tomei, Alexander William, 1930 (Folder 85)
  - Tompkins, Alva, 1931 (Folder 86)
  - Tompkins, Walker A., 1957 (Folder 87)
  - Torbert, J. K., 1938 (Folder 88)
  - Tordt, Helen S., 1934 (Folder 89)
  - Tordy, Adolph, n.d. (Folder 90)
  - Tower, John G., 1933-1966 (Folder 91)
  - Towle, H. L., 1934 (Folder 92)
  - Towle, Terence B., 1936 (Folder 93)
  - Towne, Charles F., 1919 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Townsend, H. S., 1930 (Folder 2)
  - Townsend, S. B., 1935 (Folder 3)
  - Traina, John, 1934 (Folder 4)
  - Trammell, Niles, 1940 (Folder 5)
  - Tras, Peter, 1964 (Folder 6)
  - Treadwell, George L., 1943 (Folder 7)
  - Treat, Grace D., 1928 (Folder 8)
  - Tredway, F. Q., 1943 (Folder 9)
  - Trehearne, George W., 1937 (Folder 10)
  - Tremaine, Anna G., n.d. (Folder 11)
  - Tremaine, Morris S., 1928 (Folder 12)
  - Tremaine, W. S., 1927 (Folder 13)
  - Trexler, Nonie, 1962 (Folder 14)
  - Trimble, South, 1933-1934 (Folder 15)
  - Trochet, Robert B., 1934 (Folder 16)
  - Trohan, Walter, 1954 (Folder 17)
  - Trotter, C. Lester, 1963 (Folder 18)
  - Trow, William Clark, 1958 (Folder 19)
  - Troy, Lillian Scott, 1934 (Folder 20)
  - Troyanovsky, Alexander, 1937 (Folder 21)
  - Truitt, Alfred, 1932 (Folder 22)
  - Trumball, Walter, 1939 (Folder 23)
  - Tucker, L. L., 1934 (Folder 24)
  - Tucker, Ray, 1951-1963 (Folder 25)
  - Tucker, Rufus, 1951 (Folder 26)
  - Tuckerman, J. E., 1918-1945 (Folder 27)
  - Tudor, Hugh J., 1943 (Folder 28)
  - Tudor, Ralph A., 1953 (Folder 29)
  - Tufts, James H., 1926 (Folder 30)
  - Tugman, William, 1934 (Folder 31)
  - Tugwell, Rexford G., 1937-1941 (Folder 32)
  - Tulin, Phyllis M., 1933 (Folder 33)
  - Tully, Grace G., 1932-1943 (Folder 34)
  - Tully, Paula, 1933 (Folder 35)
  - Tumulty, Joseph P., 1938 (Folder 36)
  - Turck, Charles J., 1927-1931 (Folder 37)
  - Turner, Catherine, 1952 (Folder 38)
  - Turner, Timothy G., 1954-1960 (Folder 39)
  - Turnure, David A., 1939 (Folder 40)
  - Turyn, Victor, 1963 (Folder 41)
  - Tuska, Benjamin, 1932 (Folder 42)
  - Tuttle, Roderic D., 1963 (Folder 43)
  - Tweedy, Gordon B., 1931 (Folder 44)
  - Twitchell, D. E., 1934 (Folder 45)
  - Tydings, Millard E., 1933 (Folder 46)
  - Tyler, A. Ranger, 1934 (Folder 47)
  - Tyson, James L., 1943 (Folder 48)
  - Tyson, Levering, 1931 (Folder 49)
  - Udwin, Maurice M., 1936 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Ullery, Elizabeth S., 1936 (Folder 2)
  - Umstattd, William E., 1955-1965 (Folder 3)
  - Underhill, J. L., 1963 (Folder 4)
  - Underwood, Thomas R., 1948 (Folder 5)
  - U.S. Solicitor General (See Solicitor General)
  - U.S. Supreme Court (See Supreme Court)
  - Untermeyer, Samuel, 1934 (Folder 6)
  - Upman, Frank, Jr., 1934 (Folder 7)
  - Upson, Lent D., 1927-1943 (Folder 8)
  - Urry, Donald C., 1957 (Folder 9)
  - Utt, James B., 1964 (Folder 10)
  - Vail, Harry L., 1919 (Folder 11)
  - Valency, M. J., 1927 (Folder 12)
  - Valentine, Lewis J., 1940 (Folder 13)
  - Valley, Morton T., 1950 (Folder 14)
  - Van Baalen, Henry, 1922 (Folder 15)
  - Vance, J. W., 1934 (Folder 16)
  - Vandenberg, Arthur H., 1938-1939 (Folder 17)
  - Vanderbeck, Frank H., 1942 (Folder 18)
  - Vanderbilt, Arthur T., 1947-1955 (Folder 19)
  - Vanderbilt, Cornelius, Jr., 1932-1959 (Folder 20)
  - Vanderbilt, William H., 1937 (Folder 21)
  - Vanderhoof, H. A., 1942 (Folder 22)
  - Vanderlip, Frank A., Jr., 1924-1937 (Folder 23)
  - Vanderschmidt, Fred, 1949 (Folder 24)
  - Van Der Werker, Harrison, 1932 (Folder 25)
  - Vanderzee, A., 1938 (Folder 26)
  - Van Dyck, Edward S., 1932 (Folder 27)
  - Van Gelder, Robert, 1943 (Folder 28)
  - Van Hecke, M. T., 1933 (Folder 29)
  - Van Nuys, Frederick, 1937 (Folder 30)
  - Van Ostrand, C. H., 1934 (Folder 31)
  - Van Rensselaer, Bernard S., 1964 (Folder 32)
  - Van Slyck, M. L., 1945-1954 (Folder 33)
  - Van Veen, M., 1932 (Folder 34)
  - Varga, H. E., 1921 (Folder 35)
  - Vatter, Harold G., 1960 (Folder 36)
  - Vaughan, Robert F., 1922 (Folder 37)
  - Vaux, George, 1927 (Folder 38)
  - Veiller, Lawrence, 1931 (Folder 39)
  - Verity, George M., 1936 (Folder 40)
  - Vermillion, E. C., 1922 (Folder 41)
  - Veresk, A. D., 1920 (Folder 42)
  - Vincent, Carl, 1933 (Folder 43)
  - Vicker, Ray, 1962 (Folder 44)
  - Villard, Oswald Garrison, 1927-1939 (Folder 45)
  - Vincent, W. A., 1936 (Folder 46)
  - Vinson, Robert E., 1924 (Folder 47)
  - Vizzard, John A., 1953 (Folder 48)
  - Vodola, Angelo, 1931 (Folder 49)
  - Vollmer, August, 1934 (Folder 50)
  - Von Frech, Philip, 1927 (Folder 51)
  - Vorse, Dorothy, 1963 (Folder 52)
  - Vrendenburgh, James B., 1939 (Folder 53)
  - Vrooman, C. M., 1919-1931 (Folder 54)
  - Waddell, Robert, 1954 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Wadsted, Otto, 1933 (Folder 2)
  - Wagener, Siegfried, 1934 (Folder 3)
  - Wagner, Robert F., 1937 (Folder 4)
  - Wagner, Walter F., 1941 (Folder 5)
  - Waid, Helen Elizabeth, 1934 (Folder 6)
  - Wainer, M., 1934 (Folder 7)
  - Wainscott, Clinton S., 1934 (Folder 8)
  - Waite, E. A., 1938 (Folder 9)
  - Waite, Grace, 1934 (Folder 10)
  - Waite, John Barker, 1927-1929 (Folder 11)
  - Wakeham, Frederick L., 1924 (Folder 12)
  - Walcott, E. A., 1927 (Folder 13)
  - Wald, Lillian D., 1936 (Folder 14)
  - Waldman, Louis, 1933 (Folder 15)
  - Waldo, Richard K., 1921 (Folder 16)
  - Walkden, R., 1934 (Folder 17)
  - Walker, Allen, 1924 (Folder 18)
  - Walker, Frank, 1936 (Folder 19)
  - Walker, James B., 1933-1937 (Folder 20)
  - Walker, L. C., 1952-1962 (Folder 21)
  - Walker, John, 1932 (Folder 22)
  - Walker, John Perrine, 1939 (Folder 23)
  - Walker, Raymond, n.d. (Folder 24)
  - Walker, Robert C., 1965 (Folder 25)
  - Wall, Frances, 1936 (Folder 26)
  - Wall, K. E., 1945 (Folder 27)
  - Wall Street Journal, 1943-1946 (Folder 28)
  - Wallace, DeWitt, 1955-1958 (Folder 29)
  - Wallace, Everett, 1934 (Folder 30)
  - Wallace, George, 1922 (Folder 31)
  - Wallace, Henry A., 1932-1960 (Folder 32)
  - Wallace, John H., 1938-1939 (Folder 33)
  - Wallace, Richard W., 1927 (Folder 34)
  - Wallace, Schuyler C., 1924-1941 (Folder 35)
  - Waller, H. T., 1919 (Folder 36)
  - Wallin, Mrs. William, 1933 (Folder 37)
  - Walling, Willoughby, 1955 (Folder 38)
  - Wallis, W. Allen, 1962-1963 (Folder 39)
  - Walter, M. E., 1951-1956 (Folder 40)
  - Walters, Edward, 1931 (Folder 41)
  - Walters, T. A., 1932 (Folder 42)
  - Walton, Charles W., 1930 (Folder 43)
  - Wampler, Cloud, 1943 (Folder 44)
  - Warburg, James P., 1936 (Folder 45)
  - Ward, Cornelia C., 1933 (Folder 46)
  - Ward, Frank H., 1921 (Folder 47)
  - Ward, John H., 1936 (Folder 48)
  - Ward, Margaret, 1927-1928 (Folder 49)
  - Ward, Stuart R., 1934 (Folder 50)
  - Wardell, Justus S., 1934 (Folder 51)
  - Ware, Frederick, 1944 (Folder 52)
  - Waring, J. B. H., 1935 (Folder 53)
  - Waring, T. R., 1957 (Folder 54)
  - Waring, W. J., 1956 (Folder 55)
  - Warner, Albert L., 1937 (Folder 56)
  - Warner, C. B., 1932 (Folder 57)